The whole scene
整个我们这场整个我们这场
definite
一定的一定的
It should be said that there was a beautiful encounter
应该说打了一场漂亮的遭遇战应该说打了一场漂亮的遭遇战
Very good results have been achieved
取得了非常好的成绩取得了非常好的成绩
It's the 42000200 medical staff that we rushed to aid Wuhan to fight with 100000 local medical staff in Wuhan
是我们驰援武汉的这些42000千两千名医务人员和武汉当地10万名的医务人员共同战斗是我们驰援武汉的这些42000千两千名医务人员和武汉当地10万名的医务人员共同战斗
To win the battle
才取得这场战役的胜利才取得这场战役的胜利
In this protest
这次抗议当中这次抗议当中
We should sum it up seriously
我们值得去认真的总结我们值得去认真的总结
In terms of the emergency capability this time
在这次应急能力来看在这次应急能力来看
Our country in a very short period of time
我们国家在很短的时间内我们国家在很短的时间内
The gene sequence of the new coronavirus was published
就公布了新冠病毒的基因的序列就公布了新冠病毒的基因的序列
For the world
为全球为全球
Developing vaccines
研制疫苗研制疫苗
Got time
争取到了时间争取到了时间
Including the establishment of Fang Chang
包括方昌的建立包括方昌的建立
Including the establishment of Huoshen mountain and Leishen mountain
包括火神山雷神山的建立包括火神山雷神山的建立
The reaction was very instantaneous
反应非常的瞬间反应非常的瞬间
The action was very decisive
行动非常的果断行动非常的果断
For the whole epidemic
对整个这次的疫情的对整个这次的疫情的
And reversal
和逆转和逆转
All played a vital role
都起到了至关重要的作用都起到了至关重要的作用
So we said
所以我们说所以我们说
This is the overall response
这次整体的这次反应这次整体的这次反应
It is a test of our national emergency system
是我们国家应急体系的一个考验是我们国家应急体系的一个考验
It was also a very successful exercise
也是一次非常成功的演练也是一次非常成功的演练
I think these valuable experiences
我想这些宝贵的经验我想这些宝贵的经验
In this protest
在这次抗议当中在这次抗议当中
We all deserve to sum up
我们都值得去认真的总结我们都值得去认真的总结
I think this will enrich our theoretical system of disease prevention and treatment
我想这个将丰富我们治疗疫病的一些个理论体系防治的内容我想这个将丰富我们治疗疫病的一些个理论体系防治的内容
And these values often guide us to better deal with the treatment of similar infectious diseases in the future
而这些的价值往往指导我们更好的应对以后出现了类似的传染病的治疗而这些的价值往往指导我们更好的应对以后出现了类似的传染病的治疗
So medicine is the accumulation of generations
所以医学就是一代一代的不断的积累所以医学就是一代一代的不断的积累
Continuous inheritance
不断的传承不断的传承
Continuous development
不断的发扬不断的发扬
gradual
逐渐的逐渐的
Progress
进步的进步的
But we're not saying this is the best
但是我们不是说这次至善至美但是我们不是说这次至善至美
There is still a lot to be improved
还有很多需要完善的地方还有很多需要完善的地方
We need to keep going
需要我们不断的去需要我们不断的去
Summarize and improve constantly
总结不断去提升总结不断去提升